Hy, thank you Pittsburgh for hosting us.
It's been absolutely amazing. Shout out
TO ALL MY INTERNATIONAL FANS.
With the
163rd pick in the 20
26 NFL draft, the Mininnesota Vikings
select Charles Demings, defensive back
Steven F. Austin.
>> Pretty good college football program
over there at Stephen F. Austin of late.
um believe they won a national title
here over the last two years if I
remember correctly in the FCS. Four-year
starter long. He's got good speed. He's
smooth in coverage. Just hasn't seen.
Now, he did go to the Senior Bowl and
had some ups and downs at the Senior
Bowl. Um but you know, he's a little bit
thin, which might be a concern for some
teams, at least slender. He's weighs
194. You don't really doesn't always
look that way on tape, but um there's a
little bit of a delay with his plant and
drive, some of his firing on the ball,
you feel like with his traits and his
size and his length, he needs to have a
little bit more ball production against
the level of competition he faced. So,
that's something to keep an eye on. But,
uh good traits, good length, good speed.
There's a lot of ingredients to work
with.
>> Yeah, a lot of ingredients. And
sometimes when you have a guy coming
from a small school, you got to give him
grace when it comes to making that
transition up to the the big leagues.
And he came and you talked about the ups
and downs at the senior bowl. Some of
that is to be expected. And you going to
see him go through some of those ups and
downs in training camp. What you hope is
his confidence stays intact and he has
the ability to take his game to another
level as we get closer to the regular